[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Tasmanian devil cartoon character from Looney Tunes by Warner Bros.?", "correct_answer": "Taz", "incorrect_answers": ["Tess", "Devlin", "Tassie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Melanie Lynskey, who played Lurlynn in Sweet Home Alabama, has starred in many films and TV shows. In which of these movies or TV shows did she NOT appear?", "correct_answer": "CSI", "incorrect_answers": ["Coyote Ugly", "Ever After", "Two And a Half Men"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Zoophobias are some of the most widespread abnormal fears. Which of the following is not a fear associated with animals?", "correct_answer": "Neophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Entomophobia", "Cynophobia", "Felinophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many colonies formed United States of America in 1776?", "correct_answer": "13", "incorrect_answers": ["51", "50", "7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor played the young man who was Juror #5 in the movie 12 Angry Men?", "correct_answer": "Jack Klugman", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Balsam", "E.G. Marshall", "Joseph Sweeney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Its a Wonderful Life, what was Clarences rank?", "correct_answer": "AS2-Angel Second Class", "incorrect_answers": ["A.I.T- Angel in Training", "rookie", "A2C-Angel Second Class"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1939 movie A Tale of Two Cities, Ronald  Coleman played both Charles Darnay and Sydney Carlton.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Elvis Presleys second number 1hit?", "correct_answer": "Dont Be Cruel", "incorrect_answers": ["Love Me Tender", "Hound Dog", "Heartbreak Hotel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Raspberry Award for Worst Picture for 1992 was given to this movie.", "correct_answer": "Shining Through", "incorrect_answers": ["Final Analysis", "Christopher Columbus: The Discovery", "The Bodyguard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress starred in the 1996 disaster movie Twister?", "correct_answer": "Helen Hunt", "incorrect_answers": ["Meg Ryan", "Jodie Foster", "Michelle Pfeiffer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Sonnys last visitor to the bank in the film Dog Day Afternoon?", "correct_answer": "his mother", "incorrect_answers": ["his cousin", "his father", "his sister"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What people worshipped the sun god and god of war Huitzilopochtli?", "correct_answer": "The Aztecs", "incorrect_answers": ["The Chinese", "The Celts", "The Cheyenne"]}]